[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On the Black Dog soundtrack, who sang the song Drivin My Life Away?", "correct_answer": "Rhett Atkins", "incorrect_answers": ["Big House", "Gary Allan", "Marty Stewart"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This type of orchid, discovered by Charles Darwin, is pollinated by the hawkmoth, an insect with a long tongue.", "correct_answer": "The Comet Orchid", "incorrect_answers": ["Stargaser", "Clivia miniata", "Sundew"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the longest river in Asia  Minor?", "correct_answer": "Euphrates", "incorrect_answers": ["Tigris", "Ganges", "Mekong"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is a major US airline and a subsidiary of Delta Air Lines?", "correct_answer": "Northwest Airlines", "incorrect_answers": ["Northeast Airlines", "Southwest Airlines", "Southeast Airlines"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the building in which the movie Die Hard is set?", "correct_answer": "Nakatomi Plaza", "incorrect_answers": ["Plateroplit Plaza", "Chingawang Plaza", "Macamoni Plaza"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Early Colorado ranchers raised cattle, sheep, hogs, chickens, and turkeys, with the main focus on cattle.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Actor Lee Marvin was originally offered the role of shark bounty hunter Quint in the movie Jaws.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The consumption of what type of bread is forbidden on the holiday of Passover according to Jewish laws?", "correct_answer": "Leavened bread", "incorrect_answers": ["Toasted bread", "All of these", "Flat bread"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 1000 people, how many would be non-religious (that is: Atheist, Agnostic, Secular Humanist, No preference)?", "correct_answer": "171", "incorrect_answers": ["482", "2", "23"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1933 movie Duck Soup, starring the Marx brothers, was really about duck soup.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Smokey and the Bandit, the characters from the self-titled movie, had to take beer from Texarkana, Texas and to deliver it to which city?", "correct_answer": "Atlanta, GA", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Mobile, AL", "Conyers, GA"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the last thing humans do in the fictional story of Bambi?", "correct_answer": "Start a forest fire", "incorrect_answers": ["Kill Mulet", "Capture Bambi for a zoo.", "Kill Bambi"]}]